England
Marist College
England
1789 1984
Marist Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road, Poughkeepsie, New York 12601
Lowell Thomas
2.1.1.2.4
1203 Linear feet
Items in this collection do not circulate and may be used in-house only.
Glass plate negatives; England
- Lowell Thomas Papers
  - Graphic Materials, 2
    - Photographs, 2.1
      - Glass plate negatives, 2.1.1
        - Lowell Thomas, 2.1.1.2
          - England, 2.1.1.2.4
              - Girl driving Australian soldiers, London, circa 1918; 9 (Box 1322)
                3.5x4.5
              - Australian soldier with arm around girl, sitting on Balustrade, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 10
              - Girl with arm around Australian soldier, American soldier in one corner, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 11
              - Australian soldier holding child, sitting on bench, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 12
              - Canadian soldier with arm around girl, surrounded by children, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 13
              - Soldiers and women sitting on Balustrade, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 14
              - Soldiers sitting on Balustrade, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 15
              - Soldiers sitting on Balustrade, others standing Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 16
              - Sailors and girls sitting on bench, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 17
              - Women standing in front of a statue of a lion near Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 18
              - Two women standing in front of a statue of a lion near Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 19
              - Two women, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 20
              - Two women and a soldier sitting on a bench, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 21
              - Woman standing by statue, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 22
              - Poster for the women’s land army at the base of Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 23
              - Poster for women’s land army at base of Nelson’s Column, drummers in foreground, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 24
              - Women standing in rows, circa 1918; 25
              - Crowds watching women march down street, circa 1918; 26
              - Two land army girls, London, circa 1918; 27
              - American soldier (“Doughboy””) talking to land army girls, London, circa 1918; 28
              - Four wagons filled with soldiers, circa 1918; 29
              - Wagons filled with soldiers, circa 1918; 30
              - Soldier standing in front of wagon, circa 1918; 31
              - Demonstration for State Aid for the Blind, Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 32
              - Demonstration for State Aid for the Blind, three soldiers and woman and foreground, Nelson’s Column, Trafalgar Square, London, circa 1918; 33
              - Four girls standing in front of a white craft airplane model, London, circa 1918; 34
              - American soldier and London horse Guard, circa 1918; 35
              - American soldier, sailor and London horse Guard, circa 1918; 36
              - Three soldiers and woman, with dog, in front of tents, London, circa 1918; 37
              - British soldiers sewing socks, London, circa 1918; 38
              - Soldiers leaving a Y.M.C.A, circa 1918; 39
              - Group of soldiers and sailors, American Y.M.C.A in background, London, circa 1918; 40
              - Street scene, poster for American Y.M.C.A. in foreground, circa 1918; 41
              - Street scene, Canadian Y.M.C.A., Hotel Cecil in background, London, circa 1918; 42
              - Street scene, double-decker buses, Morley’s Hotel, London, circa 1918; 43
              - Street scene, double-decker bus, Morley’s Hotel, London, circa 1918; 44
              - Charing Cross Hotel, circa 1918; 45
              - Two men on horses, Victorian Hotel in background, circa 1918; 46
              - Whitehead and his two children in garden, London, circa 1918; 47
              - Whitehead’s home, house and lawn, circa 1918; 48
              - Whitehead’s home, lawn and waterfront, London, circa 1918; 49
              - Whitehead’s home, lawn, two people in distance, London, circa 1918; 50
              - Washington Inn, soldier on bench in foreground, statue in distance, London, circa 1918; 51
              - Washington Inn, soldiers in foreground, London, circa 1918; 52
              - Balloon automobile in front of the Oceanic House, London, circa 1918; 53
              - Westminster Abbey, London, circa 1918; 54
              - Westminster Hospital, Big Ben in distance, London, circa 1918; 55
              - Wellington Arch, soldier in foreground, London, circa 1918; 56
              - Large statue with lions at base, circa 1918; 57
              - Woman standing by lamppost, buildings in distance, London, circa 1918; 58
              - Two men standing near ornate fence, large building in distance, London, circa 1918; 59
              - Crowd of people in park, circa 1918; 60
              - Four military men talking next to man holding advertisement for baseball game, circa 1918; 61
                4x5
              - Three military men walking away from building, circa 1918; 62
              - Two military men talking next to Sphinx replica, London, circa 1918; 63
              - Two women wearing “Royal Flying Corps” uniforms on motorcycle and sidecar, circa 1918; 64
              - Three people sitting on bench in front of fountain, circa 1918; 65
              - Crowd of people, in park, gathered around flagpole, circa 1918; 1 (Box 1323)
              - Crowd of people in park, circa 1918; 2
              - Chelsea Football Club, spectators watching game, circa 1918; 3
              - Chelsea Football Club, cricket match, circa 1918; 4
              - Chelsea Football Club, cricket match, circa 1918; 5
              - Crowd sitting near the church army, Lord Kitchener Hut, circa 1918; 6
              - Crowd near the church army, Lord Kitchener Hut, circa 1918; 7
              - Couple sitting in field, crowd in background, circa 1918; 8
              - Canadian soldier, woman and child sitting in field, crowd in background, circa 1918; 9
              - Little boy, saluting, wearing H.M.S. diadem hat, circa 1918; 10
                5x7
              - Little girl wearing hat from the H.M.S. Queen Mary, circa 1918; 11
              - English submarine, circa 1918; 12
                3.5x5.5
              - English submarine, circa 1918; 13
              - Man with binoculars, circa 1918; 14
              - English submarine, man using binoculars, circa 1918; 15
              - Officer of an English submarine, circa 1918; 16
                3.25x4.25
              - Officers of English submarines, circa 1918; 17
              - Crew and officers, English submarine, circa 1918; 18
              - Person wearing long coat, British Submarine, circa 1918; 19